<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><title>CIS 2200 Fall 2017 - announcements</title><link href="https://cis2200al.github.io/" rel="alternate"></link><link href="https://cis2200al.github.io/feeds/announcements.atom.xml" rel="self"></link><id>https://cis2200al.github.io/</id><updated>2017-09-20T00:00:00-04:00</updated><entry><title>New Site, Week 3 &amp; Group Formation</title><link href="https://cis2200al.github.io/sep20.html" rel="alternate"></link><published>2017-09-20T00:00:00-04:00</published><updated>2017-09-20T00:00:00-04:00</updated><author><name>Anh Luong</name></author><id>tag:cis2200al.github.io,2017-09-20:/sep20.html</id><summary type="html">&lt;p&gt;Hi everyone,&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Just want to give you an overview of what you need to know and complete this week.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;New Site&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Syllabus &amp;amp; Schedule&lt;/strong&gt; You can find the Syllabus and Tentative Schedule Outline by clicking on "Syllabus" and "Schedule" on the top of the site. The schedule is not fixed, and …&lt;/p&gt;</summary><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Hi everyone,&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Just want to give you an overview of what you need to know and complete this week.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;New Site&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Syllabus &amp;amp; Schedule&lt;/strong&gt; You can find the Syllabus and Tentative Schedule Outline by clicking on "Syllabus" and "Schedule" on the top of the site. The schedule is not fixed, and there might be some minor changes in the content we cover in some weeks. I will send out announcements in advance if such changes occur. Similarly, in the case that the Syllabus needs changes in some details as the semester progresses, I will inform you of them in the syllabus.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Assignments&lt;/strong&gt; For each week, I will post the assignments' requirements here, you can click on "Assignments" at the top of the site, and find the assignments according to the weeks there. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Materials&lt;/strong&gt; This page provides you with what you need to learn each week - lecture slides, readings (textbook &amp;amp;/or articles), and videos. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;It is important and required that you always check the pages "Announcements", "Materials", and "Assignments" for each week.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Resources&lt;/strong&gt; This page is meant to be a convenient hub of important links, some of which you are required to use for the readings and assignments of the class (blacboard, textbook, google drive), some of which are optional and serve as additional resources that can benefit your studying.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;Week 3 Requirements&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;To access lecture slides, find out about the required readings, and video watching for week 3, go to &lt;strong&gt;Materials&lt;/strong&gt; &amp;gt; &lt;strong&gt;Week 3 Materials&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;To view week 3 assignments, go to &lt;strong&gt;Assignments&lt;/strong&gt; &amp;gt; &lt;strong&gt;Week 3 Assignments&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;NOTE&lt;/strong&gt;: to submit your homework, email to this address: &lt;strong&gt;athluong@gmail.com&lt;/strong&gt; with subject &lt;strong&gt;"Week 3 Assignment"&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;Group Formation&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In the following weeks, there will be some weeks that I will assign homework exercises for groups.  Additionally, there will be group projects (Excel &amp;amp; Access).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Thus, it is important that you form groups of &lt;strong&gt;3 members&lt;/strong&gt; as soon as possible &lt;strong&gt;(preferably by mid-week next week, so you guys can complete the written assignments in groups for next week)&lt;/strong&gt;. Since our class has 61 students, one group will have 4 members.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I have created a google spreadsheet and you can enter your names according to the groups that you have formed. The link to the google spreadsheet is posted in the page "Resources" ("Group List").&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Let me know if you have any questions.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Best,&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Anh Luong&lt;/p&gt;</content></entry></feed>